http://www.flyboynaturals.com/privacy-policy/

Sachets & Petal Cones
Loading... Please wait...
Welcome to flyboynaturals.com
20% Petal Sale Use Coupon: PetalSale20 - Minimum $40 Purchase
Sachets & Petal Cones
20% OFF Petal Sale - Save 20% with Coupon Code: PetalSale20 - Minimum $40 Purchase - Enjoy Free Ground Shipping on Orders Over $99*
Choose Options
Bridal White/Ivory Preserved Freeze-dried Rose Petals-Fragrant
What our Customers Say
Petals galore! Most searches for flower petals turn up synthetic petals, but we needed natural ones for the flower girl to toss at our farm wedding. Flyboy has a range of color and price options, and lots of informative detail about how many petals you might need for what you're trying to use them for. Shipping was quick and easy after ordering. Highly recommend ordering from them!." Patty Liao , married on 10/27/2018 Reviewed on 11/27/2018
More Testimonials >>
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (website address).
This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It
will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through
the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your
information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have
access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other
direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you
contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of
our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship
an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell
you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the
following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number
given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive
information via the website, your information is protected both online and
offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that
information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify
this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or
looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online,
we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the
information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service)
are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers
in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure
environment.
Sign up for latest promotions and deals.
Mon to Sat:
10am - 10pm (EST)
7am - 7pm (PST)
© 2020 Flyboy Naturals, Inc.All Rights Reserved. Bigcommerce Custom Design & Development
Back to Top
Close Window
Join Our Mailing ListSign up & Receive the latest Discounts and Promotions
Don’t show again!
